teens-love-oldmen.com 2018-10-20

# Privacy Policy Problem Master BV

Problem Master B.V.

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for mature.nl. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. This page was last updated on July 7th 2016.

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address on our website or the unsubscribe link in the email.

### Registration

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

### Orders

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like your email address, name and shipping address). This information is used to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

### Updates

Our privacy policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

### Questions and Contact Information

All questions regarding this provacy policy must be directed to: support@mature.nl
